http://www.mlnlaw.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutPractice AreasNewsReviewsContact
MenuHomeAboutPractice AreasNewsReviewsContactYou pay nothing unless we win. Tell us about your serious injury or wrongful death. 404-531-9700Privacy PolicyWe value your privacy very highly. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the www.neffinjurylaw.com or www.mlnlaw.com Website (the “Website”) operated by the Law Offices of Michael L. Neff, P.C., this Privacy Policy contains important information regarding your privacy and how we may use the information we collect about you.Your access to and use of the Website is conditional upon your acceptance of and compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to everyone, including, but not limited to: visitors, users, and others, who wish to access or use the Website.By accessing or using the Website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any part of the Privacy Policy, then you do not have our permission to access or use the Website. What information may we collect and storeWe receive and store any and all information that you enter on this Website or provide to us by any other form of communication, including, but not limited to: electronic mail, regular mail, and phone calls.The information that we collect and store includes information that may be used to identify you, such as name and email.Collection of Non-Personal InformationWe may collect the following non-personal information:Domain and/or IP Address;What type of internet browser you are using; What brought you to our site;The pages you have accessed. Any non-personal information collected is for our internal purposes and not for sale to third parties.  We primarily use this information for evaluating, maintaining, and improving our site. Collection of Personal InformationWe do not collect personal information about you unless you voluntarily submit it to us. We do not sell or provide any information collected on this site to outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass marketing. If you do choose to give us personal information, we may use it to understand your legal needs, for our own record keeping, and to use with third party legal entities who may need this information to evaluate your legal needs.  CookiesA cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on your computer by your web browser. The file is added once you agree to store cookies on your computer or device, and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow sites to respond to you as an individual. The Website can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.This Website collects cookies and may use cookies for reasons including, but not limited to:Analyze our web traffic using an analytics package.Identify if you are signed in to the Website.Test content on the Website.Store information about your preferences.Recognize when you return to the Website. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better Website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This setting may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website. Analytics ProgramsThis Website uses Google Analytics and other analytics programs to collect information about you and your behaviors. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics, please visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/. How We May Use Your InformationWe may use the information that you provide us for the following: analytics, contact you, answer questions, and send you email newsletters. Sale of Your InformationWe do not sell your personal information.  Third-Party WebsitesThis Website may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by parties other than us. We provide such hyperlinks for your reference only. We do not control such websites and are not responsible for their contents or the privacy or other practices of such websites. It is up to you to read and fully understand their Privacy Policies. Our inclusion of hyperlinks to such websites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such websites or any association with their operators. Do Not Track SignalsDo Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. We do not support Do Not Track (” DNT “). You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. Opting Out of Us Collecting Personal InformationYou may opt-out of us collecting your personal information at any time by not inputting data into our website, by clicking unsubscribe on emails, and by contacting us. Changes to Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to amend this policy at any time without any prior notice to you. QuestionsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Let's Talk: 404-531-9700
3455 Peachtree Rd. NE Ste. 509
Atlanta, GA 30326
Facebook
info@neffinjurylaw.comSite Created by New TricksDisclaimer | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy© 2020 Neff Injury Law
